# Nazanin Akbari . Jarvis Consulting

My bachelor degree is in the field of Biomedical engineering. I have two years of work experience as a biomedical engineer in 5Azar hospital, Gorgan, Iran. I started my master degree at Concordia university, Montreal, QC in 2019. I got my master degree from Concordia university in the field of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science. At Concordia university, I did multiple projects in signal processing, image processing, Hardware verification and designing website for Airline reservation system. In Montreal, I also learned French language, B1 level. I like software industry because this field is incredibly broad. I am passionate to learn new things and expand my knowledge and experience. I love to solve problems and help people to experience a better and easier life.

#### Skills

Proficient: Java, Python, Google Cloud Platform, Linux/Bash, Visual Studio

Competent: Agile/Scrum, RDBMS/SQL, Git, Docker and Containerization, Intellij IDE

Familiar: Neural Network, Machine Learning, C#, Azure DevOps, Unit testing

## **Jarvis Projects**

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis\_data\_eng\_NazaninAkbari

Linux Cluster Resource Monitoring App [GitHub]: Implemented Linux-SQL project, to help Jarvis Linux Cluster Administration (LCA) record the hardware specification of 10 servers running CentOS7 which are connected to each other throughout a switch. The project is implemented by using Bash scripts, Docker containers, Postgres database, and SQL queries.

#### **Highlighted Projects**

Website for Airline reservation system: Designed an Airline Reservation System application which enables the customers to search and book the flights in general. The project has been designed in C# technology and consists of a SQL server as the database of the project.

Snake game [GitHub]: Designed Snake game using Python. The snake game has a snake that you can control it by using your keyboard to grab the food. It grows in length as uses food. You have to make sure that you don't end up getting tangled or hitting the wall and the goal is to eat as much food as you can while staying alive.

**Pong game** [GitHub]: Designed Pong game using Python. It's basically just a ball that's going across a table and two players each control a paddle bouncing the ball back and forth. If you miss the ball, then the other player scores a point.

Turtle crossing game [GitHub]: Designed Turtle crossing game using Python. The player controls the turtle which can only go forwards, and there's a whole bunch of randomly generated cars which are going horizontally across the screen. Once a player reaches the other side of the screen, the cars speed up, but the player goes back to the starting position, ready to cross the screen again. At some point when the player turtle hits a car, then that is game over.

### **Professional Experiences**

Software Developer, Jarvis (2021-present): Developed a monitoring system with Postgres database.

Biomedical engineer, 5Azar hospital, Gorgan, Iran (2016-2018): As a biomedical engineer, I was responsible for eight direct employees. Analyzing technical defects and implement data-driven solution with engineering guidance, Prioritizing work load effectively and complete all work assignments in a timely manner, Controling my team member hours to hit monthly targets while maintaining above 100% productivity are part of my roles. I always took responsibility of situations and errors of myself or my team members and also I Insisted on highest standards (I never cut the corners).

#### Education

Concordia university (2019-2021), Master of Electrical engineering and Computer Science, Electrical and Computer Engineering - GPA: 3.6/4.3

Azad university, Tehran, Iran (2013-2016), Bachelor of Biomedical Engineering, Electrical and Computer Engineering - Identified as exceptional talent, Azad University, Tehran, Iran (2014) - GPA: 3.62/4.3 - Scholarship

# Miscellaneous

- Udemy Scrum certificate (2021)
- Reading
- Walking
- Cooking